(Priya:)Mmm, me, too.
You know, I was thinking:
(Leonard:)There are some great
research facilities in India.
(Priya:)Where are you going
with this, Leonard?
Well, I'm just saying, you know,
I don't have any real ties here,
(Leonard:)so if I were to move to New
Delhi, we could, you know--
(Leonard:)go out.
(Priya:)Leonard, didn't we have this
conversation five years ago?
(Leonard:)Well, yes, but...
(Leonard:)things have changed.
(Leonard:)You know, you're older,
I'm older--
(Leonard:)Look, no more
superhero bed sheets.
(Priya:)Sweetheart,
(Priya:)just because we have fun when
I come to town doesn't mean
(Priya:)I want to have a
serious relationship.
(Leonard:)It doesn't?
(Priya:)Mm-mm.
(Priya:)And besides, I could never bring
a white boy home to my parents.
(Priya:)They'd have a cow.
(Priya:)Which is a much
bigger deal in India.
(Leonard:)I'm not that white.
My great-great-grandmother
was half Cherokee.
(Leonard:)I know that's not the right kind
of Indian, but it is something.
(Priya:)You're funny.
(Priya:)Leonard?
(Sheldon:)What?